For bug reporting, please fill out the following form with as much details as possible, so we can track down the issue

1. Brief description of the issue
2. What firmware and UI version are you using?
3. Windows version?
4. Which feature is broken?
5. Does it occur frequently? (Rarely, sometimes, always, etc.)
6. Steps to re-produce the issue?
7. Screenshots and logs
8. Other information

(A github issue is preferred for better bug tracking)